我家有个毕业生了
My progeny has joined the ranks of the graduated.
你帮我申请的这些大学吗
You applied to all those schools for me?
还有几所保底的  以防万一
A few fallbacks, too, just in case.
你又不是我妈  我想跟谁说话你管不着
You're not my mother, you're not in charge of who I talk to,
我上不上大学你他妈更管不着
and you're sure as shit not in charge of if I go to college!
我们都日得长茧了  可我还是怀不上
We've been banging like bunnies, and I can't get pregnant.
你打算怎么办
What'll you do?
你疯了吗
Are you out of your fucking mind?
小凯和你只是为了生育  又不是做爱
Kev is just gonna lie down with you for procreation, not sex.
谢谢你了  老妈
Wham, bam, thank you, mom.
你干嘛穿我衣服
What are you doing wearing my top?
沾沾你的女人味儿
Pheromones, I'm borrowing them.
男人不就喜欢你这个嘛
It's the thing boys like about you.
你是说奶子
You mean tits?
恐怕你还得等上一两年
I think you might be a year or two off.
但你却要娶一个靠跟男人上床维生的女人
Are you gonna marry someone who screws guys for a living?
谁在乎  就他妈是张纸而已
Who gives a shit? It's a fucking piece of paper.
你爱我
You love me.
就这一次  承认吧
Just this once, fucking admit it.
我想入伍
I want to enlist.
下趟去基础战斗训练营的巴士是什么时候
When's the next bus to basic combat training?
明天一早
Tomorrow morning.
菲利普
Philip.
是利普
It's Lip.
现在起叫你加拉格  上车
It's just Gallagher now. Get on.
你最近见过吉米吗
I was wondering if you'd seen Jimmy lately.
如果出现冲突的迹象  或是事情进展的不如他意
Any sign of conflict, things not going his way,
他就会消失
and he just disappears.
那是他的一贯作风了
It's what he does.
拿出点儿男人样来
Be a man.
上船
Get onto the boat.
我能给菲奥娜打个电话吗  求你了
Can I just make one phone call to Fiona, please?
这是我最后一通留言  我发誓
Last message, I promise.
不管你在哪  再见
Wherever you are, bye.
你就是那个临时工吗
You the temp?
是的  我叫菲奥娜·加拉格
Yes. Fiona Gallagher.
普拉特先生要和你谈话
Mr. Pratt is asking for a word with you.
-让我来猜猜  他是老板  -不是大老板
- Let me guess, he's the boss. - Not the big boss,
但确实是领导
but he is a supervisor, yes.
我们貌似把派对扔一边了
We sort of ditched the party.
那你最好别勾引我
Well, then you better behave yourself,
因为我已经醉到没办法拒绝你了
because I am way too drunk not to invite you back to my tent right now.
他说你再不戒酒就会死
They said if you don't stop drinking, you're gonna die.
所以我应该戒酒
So I'm just supposed to stop drinking so that
好让你不内疚
you don't feel guilty?
你应该为了家里那些
You're supposed to stop drinking
爱你的孩子们而戒酒
because you have children at home who love you.
如果我不想改变呢
What if I don't want to change?
我就会知道我的噩梦会成真
Then I would know what I've always feared is true,
你他妈一点都不在乎我们
that you don't give a shit about any of us.
无耻家庭
第四季第一集
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：  爱卿遛小鸟      君君      重案组李Sir
■
翻译：  扎克不渣       Greentie
时间轴：  加森
■
校对： Greentie      落
后期： 孤帆          总监： 落
■
卡尔
Hey, Carl.
Carl, hey.
有跟芝加哥熊队的队服借我穿去看比赛吗
You got any bears stuff I can wear to the game today,
帽子  运动衫  都行
like a hat or a Jersey or something?
有件"操翻杰·卡尔特"的T恤
I got a "Fuck Jay Cutler" T-shirt.
芝加哥熊队的四分卫
不过上面可能有血
It might have blood on it, though.
谢谢  还是算了吧
Thanks, but no thanks.
早上好  小家伙
Morning, sunshine.
早上好
Good morning.
别在上面睡得太享受
Don't get too comfortable up there.
伊恩回来会想睡他自己的床
Ian's gonna want his old bed back when he comes home.
你上哪儿去
Where are you going?
-外面  -周日早上
- Out. - On a Sunday morning?
你穿的是我的靴子吗
Are those my boots?
-有人  -我要撒尿
- Occupied! - I got to take a piss!
-滚远点  -用楼下的卫生间
- Go away! - Use the downstairs bathroom.
还要下楼呢
It's downstairs.
年纪轻轻  要多运动
You're young. You'll live.
绝对不行  不许在阳台上撒尿
No, absolutely not. No more peeing off the balcony.
搞什么
What the fuck?
卡尔
Carl!
早啊  芭比亚克太太
Morning, Mrs. Babiak.
这儿不有厕所吗
There's a toilet right there.
芭比亚克太太可不想看你的小器官
Mrs. Babiak doesn't need an anatomy lesson.
拜托  芭比亚克太太就等着小爷我成年那天呢
Please, Mrs. Babiak's got my 18th birthday circled on her calendar.
-像人一样用厕所  -我能睡利普以前的房间吗
- Use the toilet like a human. - Can I have Lip's old room?
-不行  -他都去上大学了
- No. - He's at college.
说真的   别再随地撒尿了
Seriously, cut the shit with the nature whizzing,
不然你就别想住这儿了
or you won't live here anymore.
那个爱吃饺子的讨厌鬼会报警的
That pierogi-eating prune will call the cops.
还有  你不能住利普的房间
And no, you can't have Lip's old room.
暑假和节假日他都会回来住
He's gonna be home in the summer and for holidays.
要去混夜店吗
Oh, you going clubbing?
和霍莉一起玩而已
Hanging out with Holly.
你俩是要去站街吗
Are you two gonna work the corner?
闭嘴  青春痘小子
Shut up, zit head.
至少我还有痘痘  没阴毛姑娘
At least I got zits, no-pubes girl.
够了  都别说了
Okay, enough, both of you.
燕麦给我  老弟
Cereal, brother.
周日早上这身打扮去霍莉家
You think you might be a little overdressed
会不会有点过
for Sunday morning at Holly's?
我们又不是去教堂
It's not like we're going to church.
你今天要照看利亚姆  记得吗
You're watching Liam today, remember?
我可没像你们一样滥用大麻
I haven't abused marijuana like the rest of you,
-所以  我当然记得  -我要跟麦克去约会
- so yes, I remember. - I have the Mike thing.
我说了  我记性好得很
I said my memory's intact.
人行道上好大的黄色冰块
Big, yellow icy spot on the sidewalk.
滑得我差点把蘸酱丢了
I almost dropped the dip.
史派克肯定又在围栏外面干坏事了
Spike must've chewed through his fence again.
我鼎鼎有名的洋蓟墨西哥胡椒蘸酱
My world famous artichoke-jalapeno dip.
埃迪的最爱
Eddie loved it.
他以前常把酱抹在华夫饼上
He used to spread it on his waffles.
希拉  谢谢  闻着就好吃
Thanks, Sheila. It smells great.
她怎么又来了
Why is she here again?
我才不管  至少她把衣服都洗了
I don't care. Our laundry's clean.
-伊恩联系你了吗  -没有
- Any new texts from Ian? - Uh, no.
你今早看过手机吗
You check your phone this morning?
-看了  -都快一周了
- Yes. - It's been almost a week.
他想回来自然会回来
He'll be back when he's back.
我们应该去警局报失踪人口
We should file a missing persons report.
不用报警
We are not going to the police, okay?
他都17岁了
He's 17.
虽然这不是什么好事  但我相信他
We don't have to be happy about it, but I trust him.
也难怪他从这鬼地方逃走
No surprise he ran away from this gulag.
没人关心我们的死活
It's not like anyone gives a damn if any of us live or die!
利亚姆
Liam?
我知道  你都唠叨多少遍了
I heard you the first 300 billion times.
-270块  -产前检查本来就不便宜
- $270? - Prenatal visits aren't cheap,
苏西医生要求预付现金
and Dr. Susie is cash up front.
免费诊所有什么不好
What's wrong with the free clinic?
你忍心让孩儿妈跟浑身性病的妓女
You want your baby mama waiting hours
还有没牙的瘾君子一起排长龙吗
next to crab-infested hookers and toothless crackheads?
我上周给你的200块呢
What happened to the 200 that I gave you last week?
B超  孕期维他命
Uh, ultrasounds, prenatal vitamins,
然后我又在商场
and then I found this cute, little, black
看见一件漂亮的黑色孕妇装
maternity number at Nordstroms, too.
我说得没错吧
See what I'm saying?
小凯  你有芝加哥熊队的运动衫能借我穿一下吗
Hey, Kev, you got a Bears Jersey I can borrow?
麦克今天要带我去看比赛
Mike's taking me to the game today.
你是用完就还
Borrow as in I get it right back,
还是趁机再也不还了
or borrow as in you plan to keep it forever
并且忘了那根本不是你的
and forget it isn't yours?
用完就还  我保证
Get it right back, promise.
你还是不能吃热狗
You still staying away from hot dogs
和生芝士
and unpasteurized cheese?
还有豆芽
And no sprouts.
我知道你喜欢在时时乐沙拉吧狂吃那个
I know how you love to shovel it in at the Sizzler salad bar.
亲爱的  我怀你的时候还嗑药呢
Honey, I was still doing coke when I was pregnant with you,
现在你还担心我吃芝士
and now you worried about me eating cheese?
好了  卡罗
All right, Carol,
不许去逛商场  听见没
no Nordstroms, okay? Do you hear me?
不许去逛商场
No Nordstroms.
去二手店买点宽松运动裤和慕慕袍
Sweatpants and Adele's old muumuus from Goodwill.
我去完教堂会去一趟的
I'll stop by after church.
我们可以去买一些好走的鞋
We can go shopping for some sensible shoes.
我的脚已经开始肿了
My feet are starting to spread.
一个月后  我估计就能用脚掌滑水了
In a month, I'm gonna be able to water-ski without the skis.
好了  谢谢  再见
All right, thanks. Bye.
再见  妈妈
Bye, mama.
我们不可能负担得起医院产房了
There's no way we can afford the maternity ward.
她只能在楼上的浴缸里生
She's just gonna have to have the baby upstairs in the tub.
我们可以找街尾的特妮莎来帮忙接生
We can get Tinisha from down the block to help out.
特妮莎又不是产婆
Tinisha's not a midwife.
不  但她生过一卡车的娃
No, but she's had a shitload of babies.
威廉·冰箱·派利
William "The Refrigerator" Perry.
这人怎么取名叫冰箱
There's a player named after a kitchen appliance?
是曾经
Was.
你妈公司没有给她办医疗保险吗
Your mom doesn't have health insurance at work?
没有  如果我早知道她没有医保
No. And I would've never agreed
我是绝对不会同意干自己的岳母的
to bang my own mom-in-law if I had known she wasn't covered.
你和麦克开始认真了吗
You and Mike getting serious?
也不是说陷入爱河什么的
I mean, I'm not, like, falling in love or anything,
但我挺喜欢他
but I like him.
性生活愉快吗
The sex good?
还有待发现
I don't know yet.
初次约会就上床的菲奥娜
First-date Fiona?
那个在温迪餐厅外卖窗口
The girl who puts out waiting in line
排队时都能跟人搞上的女孩
at the Wendy's drive-through?
谁告诉你这事的  卢尼·芬尼根吗
Who told you that? Ronny Finnegan?
本·托特曼
Ben Troutman.
天啊  你还干过不止一次呀
Jesus Christ, you've done that more than once?
你和麦克什么事都没发生吗
So nothing at all with you and Mike?
也就干蹭过几次  帮他打过几次飞机
A little dry humping, a couple of hand jobs.
但没实打实的来过  他是我上司  得悠着点
But no, he's my boss, so we're going slow.
可能中产阶级不流行见面就上床
Maybe they don't fuck right away in the middle class.
真的好奇怪
It's definitely weird.
他不会强迫我  那样的话我就得决定
He doesn't, like, force himself onto me where I've got to decide
是用电击枪电晕他  还是从了他
if I'm gonna taser him or go along,
我对附近这一带的雄性就是这样
like I do with the guys from around here.
还是没有吉米的消息吗
Still nothing from Jimmy?
随风而逝  音讯全无
In the wind. Not a word.
干他娘的  反正他也是个孬种
Well, fuck him. He was a pussy anyway.
-也没有弗兰克的消息吗  -没有
- And no Frank? - Nope.
谢谢上帝的小恩小惠
Oh, thank Jesus for small blessings.
没有他  你会过得更好
You're better off without him.
不  他会回来的  弗兰克就像蟑螂
No, he'll be back. Frank's a cockroach.
你可以踩他  用杀虫剂喷他  试着淹死他
You can stomp on him, spray him, try and drown him,
但他总会从粪坑里再爬回来
but he always comes crawling back up out of the toilet bowl.
-警局  -警察
- Police department. - Police!
-警察  -举起手来  举起来
- Police! - Hands. Come on, hands!
举起手来
Hands up!
看看那边
Check over there.
-警局  -里屋安全
- Police department! - Back room clear.
警察
Police.
你以为我没看见你偷藏那玩意儿吗
What, you don't think I saw you stash that?
快点  手举起来
Come on, hands.
警察  把手举起来
Police. Show us your hands.
把手举过头顶  快点
Let me see your hands, come on.
快点  老兄  举起手来  快点
Come on, pal, hands. Let's go.
喂  举起手来
Yo, hands out, now.
弗兰克
Frank?
你好  曼迪  帽子真不错
Hi, Mandy. Nice tam.
谢谢  最近还好吗
Thanks. How you been?
很好
Good.
伊恩还是音讯全无  你有他的消息吗
Ian's still missing. Have you heard from him?
什么都没有吗
Nothing?
电话或短信都没有吗
Not even a call or a text?
抱歉
Sorry.
你想知道利普过得怎么样吗
So you want to know how Lip's doing?
不太想
Not really.
-他上大学了  -好样的
- He's in college. - Good for him.
这就是一堆账单  中餐馆的外卖单
This is a bunch of bills, chink delivery menus,
以及粘贴式美甲优惠券
and press-on nail coupons.
你是抢劫了哪个邮箱啊  迪尔伯恩救助所吗
What mailboxes you rob, The Dearborn Projects?
复式公寓大楼
Apartment complex over by rush.
有张ATM卡呢
There's an ATM card.
恭喜啊  连个密码都有没
Congratulations. It has no fucking pin number.
你打算怎么做  每天都去洗劫那同一个邮箱
What are you gonna do, rob the same mailboxes every day
直到他们把密码寄过来吗
until they send the pin?
喂  你
Hey, you...
你昨天就挣了这么点儿吗
This is all you made yesterday?
我全都给你了
I give you everything.
才220块
220 bucks?
你接了几个客
How many Johnsons did you squash?
17个
17.
打一次飞机才12块吗
That's, like, 12 bucks a wank.
-刚刚门口是谁  -黛比·加拉格
- Who was at the door? - Debbie Gallagher.
-她想干什么  -她在找伊恩
- What did she want? - She was looking for Ian.
你看见他了吗
You seen him?
-你在乎个什么劲儿  -我才不在乎
- Why do you care? - Don't.
她说利普在大学过得挺不错
She said Lip was doing good in college.
该走了  朗
It's time to go, Ron.
拜伦式英雄学习小组
Byronic heroes study group.
我得先去一趟实验室
I have to stop by the lab first.
我正为我的云城建设新码头呢
I'm building a new docking station for my cloud city.
现在就走  朗
Now, Ron.
你收到关于明天快闪活动的短信了吗
Hey, so did you get the text about tomorrow's flash mob?
什么
The what?
下午5点  老兄
5:00, man.
所有人都会保持静止60秒
Everyone's gonna freeze for exactly 60 seconds.
好吧
Okay.
3点钟时  我们会在图书馆二楼的后侧
We'll be on the second floor of the library in the back at 3:00
如果你想参加学习小组就一起来
if you want to join us for our study group.
我们不是说好了人越少越好吗
Um, we agreed to keep the group small.
我们已经有6个人了
We already have six people, so...
利普可以来  他很酷
Lip can come, he's cool.
等下再说吧  等我做完兼职
You know what, maybe later, you know, after work-study.
菲奥娜
Fiona!
-怎么了  -麦克来了
- What? - Mike.
这是什么  《电锯惊魂》吗
Ugh. What is this, Saw?
周日大清早就看这个
On a Sunday morning?
麦克是你的真名吗
Mike your real name?
是啊
Yeah.
大名叫迈克尔  不过叫麦克就行
I mean, Michael, but yeah, I'm Mike.
-偷过车吗  -什么
- Ever steal a car? - What?
在院子里烧过浸满鲜血的衣服吗
Ever burn your blood-soaked clothes in the yard?
-你准备好出发了吗  -是啊  当然了
- You ready to go? - Uh, yeah, absolutely.
好的
Uh, okay.
我大概6点钟左右回来
I'll be back around 6:00.
别把家给烧了
Don't set the house on fire.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
-不是吧  -必须的
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
我妈可能还会在你脸上涂油彩呢
Just wait till my mom paints your face.
周日早上没什么人竞拍"处女享用权"
Not much virginity-bidding action on Sunday morning.
你现在价格卖到多少了
What are you up to now?
725块
725.
"巨根约翰逊"
"Jumbo Johnson"?
听上去可能会有点吓人
Guy sounds like he could be kind of scary.
或者只是个大胖子罢了
Or just really fat.
再可怕也比不过我妈的新男友  加里
Can't be scarier than my mom's new boyfriend, Gary.
至少这家伙准备付钱
At least this guy's prepared to pay for it.
有人竞拍我的初夜吗
Anybody bid on me yet?
没有
Uh, no.
不过你把起价设那么高  没人拍也不奇怪
But not surprising with the minimum bid you set.
一百万
$1 million?
处女之身只能卖一次
You can only sell it once.
一定要让它奇货可居
Makes it an extremely rare commodity.
货源不足  价格就高  基本的经济学常识
Scarcity equals value. Basic economics.
你觉得我是在贱卖自己吗
You think I'm selling myself short?
就你而言  我觉得是营销策略不对
Well, in your case, it's kind of false advertising.
十几个男人帮她做口碑营销呢
By, like, a couple dozen dudes.
你不会真的打给那个巨根约翰逊吧
You're not really going to call that Jumbo Johnson, are you?
应该不会
Probably not.
真不公平
It's not fair.
我那个傻逼弟弟比我还小一岁
My retarded brother is a year younger than me,
他竟然都开始长腋毛了
and he's already sprouting pit hair.
你可真是幸运儿
Hey, you're lucky.
至少你可以四处鬼混且不必担心怀孕
At least you can fool around and not worry about birth control.
你怎么会需要担心避孕问题  艾丽
When did you ever worry about birth control, Ellie?
真丢人  我都13岁了
It's embarrassing. I'm 13.
来吧  我们 去商场浪荡一下
Come on, let's get slutty and head over to the arcade,
勾搭高中男生  那会让你心情好起来的
troll for high school boys. That'll cheer you up.
开门
Door!
弗兰克
Frank?
大家都去哪儿了
Where is everybody?
伊恩离家出走  利普上大学了
Ian ran away, Lip's at college,
黛比带着利亚姆去找她的荡妇朋友霍莉
Debbie took Liam somewhere with her skanky girlfriend, Holly.
-菲奥娜呢  -去看熊队比赛了
- Fiona? - Bears game.
她搞上了一个工作时认识的男人
She's banging some dude from work.
我们能拿到免费的杯子
We get free cups.
那  好吧
Well, uh, okay.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
蘸酱真不错  菲奥娜
Great dip, Fiona.
-谢谢  -看上去真美味
- Thanks. - Oh, it looks yummy.
朝鲜蓟味的吗
Artichoke?
-是啊  加上墨西哥辣椒  -祖传秘方吗
- Yeah, and jalapeno. - Family recipe?
是啊  必须的
Yeah, absolutely.
喂  小细棍
Yo, stick!
-接住  -小细棍
- Catch! - Stick?
那个  麦克小时候有点胖
Oh, well, Mike was a bit overweight as a kid.
有点
A bit?
你推一下他  他圆得都能滚起来
If you pushed him over, he'd roll.
所以  当他开始减肥以后
So when he started losing the weight,
-我们就叫他小细棍了  -才不是  那个原因呢
- we started calling him stick. - That... that is not why.
而且也不是小细棍  而是"小淫棍"
And it's not "Stick." It's "The Stick."
不不  不对
No, no. No.
别说那事  简
Don't tell that story, Jane.
事实是这样的
So here's the deal.
小麦的初恋女友艾米丽  就住在街尾那位
Mikey's first girlfriend, Emily, from down the block...
她是那种骨瘦如柴的小姑娘
She was this, like, scrawny, little girl
然后有年夏天  突然发育了
until one summer, boom!
突然之间  她的身材就变得前凸后翘
All of a sudden she's got, like, this smoking little bod.
-简  快别说了  -记得吗
- Jane, stop it. - Remember?
别说什么
Stop what?
我只是告诉菲奥娜关于艾米丽和小淫棍的故事
I'm just telling Fiona about Emily and The Stick.
-不要  -总之呢
- No! - So anyway...
-不要  快停下  -艾米丽这个小姑娘
- No, come on. - Emily's this girl.
她的腿有这么长
She's got legs, like up to here,
她说什么你都别信
Don't listen to a word she says.
她纯粹是想报复我
She's still just trying to get even with me
因为我把她的一段录像
for sending that clip in
寄给了《美国家庭滑稽录像》栏目
to America's Funniest Home Videos.
那是因为那段录像一点都不好笑  小麦
Well, that's 'cause that was not funny, Mikey, so...
好几百万人都觉得那很搞笑呢  简
A couple million people thought it was funny, Jane.
你上过《美国家庭滑稽录像》吗
You were on Funniest Home Videos?
是啊  她小时候模仿我们家狗狗的片段
Yeah, she used to, when she was a baby, imitate our dog.
麦克  有客人在呢
Mike, we have a guest.
反正  反正情况是这样的
Anyway... so anyway, here's the deal.
艾米丽来我们家的泳池玩
So Emily comes over to use our pool, right?
她穿了一件很露的比基尼
And she's got this, like, itty-bitty, little bikini on.
-好吧  -你一定记得的  对吧
- All right. - I bet you remember, don't you?
雄鸡大战开始了
Chicken war!
快来  快来  跳到我背上去
Come on. Come on. Piggyback, come on.
我想听关于小淫棍的故事呢
I want to hear the thing about The Stick!
不  不要  那都是谎话
No, you don't. It's all lies.
-好了  准备好了吗  -是的
- All right, come on. Ready? - Yeah.
马歇尔来了  从边线进攻
Here comes Marshall, streaking down the sideline.
天啊  打出了一记安打
Holy... the safety's out of position!
太棒了
Yes!
嘿[音似干草]
Hey.
-干草是给马吃的  -什么
- Hay is for horses. - Huh?
你找我有什么事吗
Can I help you with something?
老天啊
Oh, my.
你抓住他的脚
Well, you grab his feet,
我抓住他的头
and I'll grab the top end.
轻点  轻点
Gentle, gentle.
天啊
Ooh, God!
把这个垫在下面怎么样  滑过去
What about this as an under... scoop under?
弗兰克  你脏死了  脏得跟猪一样
Frank, you're filthy! You're filthy!
天啊
Jesus.
是有什么从他身上蹦出来了吗
Did something just jump off him?
大概是虫子吧
Bugs, I think.
3点钟方向  打"虫群之心"的那个
3:00, playing "The Swarm."
他们只有两个人
There are only two.
我们可不打算给你和这个小屁孩做媒
We're not trolling for you and the baby biscuit, Ellie.
只有变态才会喜欢你俩的类型
Only pervs are gonna want any part of that.
我该选哪个
Which one should I like?
你就选那个穿着帽衫的
You like the one in the Autopsy hoodie,
我就选那个钱包链外露的
and I'll like the one with the wallet chain.
我们该怎么做  直接走过去搭讪吗
So what do we do, just walk over and talk to them?
不  亲爱的
No, honey.
我们要撒下网  等着鱼儿自动上钩
We chum the waters, wait for the fish to bite.
你好  我叫黛比
Hi. Debbie.
我叫马蒂  马蒂
Matty. Matty.
来啊
Come on.
不不  我不知道怎么...
Oh, no, no. I don't know how to...
-我完全不知道该怎么做  -上  下
- I don't know what I'm doing. - Up, down.
不  你跳得挺好的
No, you're doing really good.
-是吗  -比我好多了
- Yeah? - Better than me.
就是这样
That's it.
-你学会了  -上  下
- You got it. - Up, down.
我们要给他再洗一次吗
Should we give him another bath?
已经洗三次了
Well, that's three already,
而且肥皂也用完了
and we're kind of running out of soap.
那些是不含谷蛋白的吗
These are gluten-free?
标牌上已经写明了
That's what the sign says.
-素的吗  -是大豆奶酪的  没错
- And vegan? - Soy cheese, yeah.
有花生吗
What about peanuts?
大豆奶酪匹萨中不含任何坚果
Uh, no nuts in the soy cheese pizza,
但我不敢保证
but I can't promise the
厨师没把他"坚果"放在上面
cook didn't put his nuts on the cheese pizza.
你们吃完了吗
You guys done with these?
喂  这些盘子可以收了吗
Yo, you done with these plates?
阿门  朋友
Amen, amigo.
都是一帮被惯坏了的富家子弟
Just a bunch of spoiled loath marvity.
最好别让曼尼看到你抽烟
Hey, you better not let Manny see you doing that.
他能怎么样  开除我吗
Oh, what's he gonna do, fire me?
他们又不直接付我工资
It's not like they're actually paying me.
给
Here.
你想抽个时间  一起出去玩玩吗
Hey, you want to get together sometime, hang out?
我那儿有些不错的大麻
You know, I got some decent weed.
抱歉  不行啊  老兄
Sorry, but I can't, man.
我得回去照顾老婆孩子
I got to get home to the Esposa and Ninos.
好吧
Right.
操
Fuck.
你吃过了吗
You get something to eat?
怎么了
What?
不  操  不好
No. Fuck, no.
托尼把他弄回来的
Tony brought him back.
他一直在睡觉
He's been asleep the whole time.
我想弄醒他  但他完全没有知觉
I tried to wake him, but he's out cold.
相信我  他不是在睡觉
Believe me, he's not sleeping.
真"好"啊
Great.
现在又玩上这个了吗  注射毒品
Now this? Needles?
-他真的病得很严重  -那就病着吧
- He's really sick. - Oh, he's sick, all right.
我觉得他根本下不了楼
I don't think he can make it downstairs.
-他不会惹麻烦的  -不行
- He won't be any trouble. - No.
-我没有发表意见的权利吗  -真没有
- I don't get a vote? - Not really, no.
我这就打电话给小凯  他会帮我找一张
I'm gonna call Kev, and he's gonna help me find
公园长椅  把他远远扔过去就行了
a park bench somewhere far, far away to dump him.
-他要死了  -不  他这是自寻死路
- He's dying! - No, he's killing himself.
-那是不同的  -我可以照顾他
- There's a difference. - I can take care of him.
-不行  -就要
- No. - Yes!
- No! - Yes!
好吧
Fine.
他是你带回来的  就得你来伺候
But you brought him home. He's your puppy.
他把毯子弄脏了  你就得洗干净
He makes a mess on the rug, you're cleaning it up.
谢谢  儿子
Thank you, son.
他是你的吗
Is he yours?
-谁  -那个小孩
- Who? - The little kid.
不是
Oh, no.
-我弟弟  -好吧
- Brother. - Oh, okay.
我以为他是  你儿子
Okay, I thought maybe he was, like, yours.
不是
No.
需要我开车  载你回家吗
Do you... do you want a... do you want a ride home?
你有车
You have a car?
是啊
Yeah, yeah.
不是  不是什么好车  但是
Not like a... it's not a very nice one, but yeah...
我有  我有车
yeah, I have... I have a car.
-好呀  -好的
- Sure. - Cool.
我让你  先完事儿
I'm just gonna let you, like, finish.
-好的  -好了  别说话
- All right. - Okay, just shut up.
等等  要我自己来吗
Wait, am I finishing myself here?
不  我来帮你
No, I'll... I'll help you.
好的
Okay, good.
太恶心啦
That's gross.
靠  赶紧操她把
For Christ's sake, just fuck her!
操
Fuck.
-你想我吗 我在想你 -穿着衣服想我吗
晚安  黛比
Night, Debbie.
-One dirction吗  -不  是Marina and the Diamonds
-那是谁  -你喜欢谁
你跳舞真棒  很性感
你个卖杯的小男婊
You dirty, little cup boy.
起床了
Hey, up.
上学了
Hey, school.
-做春梦了  -什么
- Wet dream? - What?
我听见你半夜呻吟来着
I heard you moaning in your sleep.
你是个加拉格家的汉子
You're a Gallagher.
天生就有性欲过剩的加拉格家的"器材"
It goes with the over-sexed glandular Gallagher equipment.
-你几岁了  10岁吗  -12岁
- What are you now, 10? - 12.
大器晚成
Late bloomer.
很正常  别担心
It's natural. Nothing to worry about.
想要加快发育的进程
The best way to stay ahead of it...
就是一天自慰几次
is to masturbate a few times a day.
自慰
Masturbate?
清醒时的自我享受
Uh, enjoying yourself while you're awake.
啊  就是撸呗
Oh, jerking off.
简单的快乐
Simple pleasures.
但是别在洗澡的时候撸
But never in the shower.
溅到浴巾上播种到你姐妹体内就不合适了
It can get on a washcloth and into your sisters.
怪胎就是这么生出来的
That's how incest babies are born.
儿子  我病了
You know, son, I'm... I'm sick.
我不能再喝酒了
I can't drink anymore,
但是我的身体仍需要酒精才能正常运转
but my body still needs alcohol to function properly.
好比机器需要油一样
It's like oil in an engine.
没有油  活塞就打不着火
The pistons just won't fire right without it.
你可以去给我找点补给品吗
Maybe you could hunt up some supplies for me?
能帮我这个忙吗  儿子
Will you do that for me, son?
帮帮我这个老头子
Help the old man out?
抱歉  宝贝儿  我有点难受
I'm sorry, baby. I'm not feeling so good.
你想让我用我又大又红的体温计
You want me to take your temperature
-来给你量体温吗  -我胃难受
- with my big, red thermometer? - Mm-mm, my stomach.
-难受了一宿  -是吗  真的吗
- Bad night. - Oh yeah? Really?
你确定
You sure?
我好像要吐了
I think I'm gonna be sick.
我就告诉你把剩下的咖喱肉扔了
You know, I told you to throw out that leftover vindaloo.
小维
Hey, "V"?
你还好吗
You okay?
需要我给你拿点什么吗
You want me to get you something?
来瓶七喜或者龙舌兰什么的
A 7-up or a shot of Tequila or something?
小维
"V"?
我一会儿就出去  亲爱的
I'll be out in a minute, honey.
能给我冲杯茶吗
Can you... can you start some tea for me, please?
逗我呢吧
You got to be shitting me.
-我果汁里有东西  -是果肉
- There's something in my juice. - It's pulp.
我们喝得起带果肉的了吗
We can afford pulp?
有了稳定的收入  蒙受"全球杯"的恩惠
Getting a steady paycheck, courtesy of worldwide cup.
怎么了
What?
-爸爸在楼上呢  -所以呢
- Dad's upstairs. - So?
-你要去打招呼吗  -不要
- Are you gonna say hi? - No.
我的午餐呢
Where's my lunch?
每人三刀买午饭吃
You're each getting $3 to buy your very own school lunch.
四刀
Four?
五刀
Five.
好吧  没问题  五刀就五刀
Fine, no problem. Five it is.
加拉格家族变土豪了
The Gallagher clan is flush.
我们已经迈向贫困线了
We're creeping up on the poverty line.
虽然还没有越过去
Haven't quite dragged ourselves over it yet,
但是至少能看见胜利的曙光了
but at least we can see it from here.
把盘子放水槽里
Hey, dishes to the sink.
要点薯条的话得六刀
It's more like six if you want worldwide cup.
不点薯条怎么样
How about we skip the chips?
早上好  大家
Good morning, everyone.
早
Morning.
今天会特别忙
Got a busy day today.
要收拾浴室
Gonna tackle the upstairs bathroom.
这可是个大挑战
That'll be a challenge.
亏了我吃了麦片
Good thing I ate my wheaties.
弗兰克今早怎么样
What's up with Frank this morning?
-看起来还那么糟  -是吗
- Still looks bad. - Yeah?
我用把他锁在屋里吗
Do I have to padlock him in the room for the day?
我觉得他起不来
I don't think he can get up.
我不想让他在屋里瞎溜达
I don't want him wandering around,
翻我的东西  把微波炉和电视当了
going through my stuff, pawning the microwave and the TV.
他想上厕所怎么办
What if he has to use the bathroom?
放学之后别忘记倒了
Don't forget to empty it when you get back from school.
我觉得连最低工资都不到  兄弟
I don't even think that's minimum wage, man.
应该受到什么法律保护之类的  对吧
There's got to be, like, a law or something, right?
肯定有
Yeah, I'm pretty sure there is,
但是我觉得不会保护"打手枪"这个工种
but I don't think it covers hand jobs.
12刀打一次  生意好的时候能才赚这么点
12 bucks a wank, that's what she makes on a fucking good day.
天呐  真的吗
Jesus, really?
我在那个泰国窑子一直付30刀
I've been paying 30 at that Thai place.
是啊  那是因为莎莎管客人多要很多钱
Yeah, but that's 'cause Sasha charges the customers
然后又从这帮女孩的工资里
a shit ton more and then
扣除很多费用
deducts all this stuff from the girls' pay.
洗衣费  房租  清洁费  设备费
Laundry, rent, janitorial, utilities.
洗手液和漱口水她都管她们要钱
She charges them for the purell and mouthwash.
她们需要组成一个工会来保护自己的权益
They need a union to protect their rights.
"国际手淫口交同行联合会"
Yeah, the international brotherhoodof hand wankers and cock suckers.
我很想在市中心大楼上看到这么个标志
I'd love to see that sign on the side of a building downtown.
是挺好
Why not?
这样的标牌太霸气了
Hey, it'd make one hell of a picket sign, though, huh?
妓女"手护"正义
"Whores united for handy Jay justice."
世界的手淫者  团结起来
Wankers of the world, unite!
-你有加拉格的信儿吗  -弗兰克  没有
- You heard from Gallagher? - Frank? No.
我以为弗兰克死了
I thought Frank was dead.
不是他妈的弗兰克  另一个  红头发的
Not fucking Frank. The other one, the redhead.
伊恩  没有  他走了
Ian? No, he took off.
怎么了  他欠你钱还是怎样
What, did he owe you money or something?
喂  找谁
Hello. Who?
有人认识菲利普先生吗
Anybody know a Mr. Phillips?
没有  抱歉  伙计
No, sorry, pal.
等等  稍等
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Hold on, yeah.
稍等
Um, hold on.
是的  我是菲利普先生
Uh, yeah, this is Mr. Phillips.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的  我待会儿过去
Yeah, I'll be over later.
怎么了
What?
斯坦  他病了
Stan. He's sick.
我下班后得去收容所
I got to go to the home after work.
谁他妈的是斯坦
Who the fuck is Stan?
这家酒吧的主人
The guy who owns the bar.
高利贷界的传奇人物
A legend among loan sharks.
当年不知道废了多少人的腿
Broke more kneecaps in his day
可比南区放高利贷的狠多了
than any other Shylock on the south side.
简直就是地狱使者
Hell of a guy.
-敬斯坦  -对  敬斯坦
- To Stan. - Yeah, Stan.
-敬斯坦  -敬斯坦
- To Stan. - To Stan.
这究竟是怎么回事
How is that possible?
一个男人的阴茎插入女人的
Well, when a man's penis goes into a woman's...
这部分不用你说我也懂
Yeah, I got that part.
我是想问  怎么我现在又能怀孕了
I mean, how is it possible now,
这两年我们尝试了各种方法都无果
after everything we've tried for the last two years?
自然母亲有时就是个爱捉弄人的婊子
Mother nature can be a tricky bitch sometimes.
怎么  你以为你只是刚好月经不调
What, did you think you were just gaining weight
然后长胖所以胸部变大了
in your breasts while you missed your period?
我压力大的时候吃得比较多
I eat a lot when I'm under stress.
什么压力
You've been under stress?
看着我老公上我老妈
Watching my husband bang my mother?
我能没有压力么
Yeah, that's been a bit stressful.
好吧  你现在可以把这些事都抛诸脑后了
Well, all of that's behind you now.
你这回确定是怀孕无疑
You're definitely pregnant.
这是好消息  维罗妮卡
This is good news, Veronica.
早上好
Good morning.
-神秘爱慕者  -我想是吧
- Secret admirer? - I guess so.
也许以后就没那么神秘了
Maybe not that secret anymore.
是吗
Really?
运输部的大卫昨天在球赛上看到你们
Dave in shipping saw you two at the bears game yesterday,
照下来发网上了
Instagramed a photo.
公司的人都关注了他
Everybody in the company follows him.
照片里的我们样子很糗吗
Were we doing something embarrassing?
拍到你们亲亲了
The kiss cam, I think.
早上好
Morning.
冲啊  熊队
Go bears, huh?
中西部区的季度报告
Uh, I am almost done with
我差不多快做完了
the quarterly Midwest regional reports.
午饭后交给你行吗
Can I get them to you after lunch?
-没问题  -好的
- No sweat. - Great.
有事吗
What?
算上今天你在这里工作就已经满三个月了
You've been working here three months as of today.
三个月  真的吗
Wow, three months? Really?
90天后  你可以享有包括医疗保险
After 90 days, your full benefits kick in,
牙科保险  退休金在内的所有福利了
medical, dental, pension.
真的吗  那太棒了
Really? That's fantastic.
是时候找你谈话了
So now it's time for the talk.
-谈话  -401K谈话
- The talk? - The 401K talk.
你想好了选哪个计划了吗
Have you decided which plan you'd like to adopt?
什么是401K
What's a 401k?
你的退休储蓄计划
Your retirement savings plan.
你符合参与条件了
You're eligible to participate.
每个月  你工资中一部分会存入401K
Every month, you deposit part of your salary into your 401k,
公司会帮你存剩下的部分  免税的
and the company matches it, tax-free.
我一部分的工资
Deposit part of my salary?
但是资产配置组合这部分
But the big decision is the asset allocation mix
就由你自己选了
you decide to elect.
货币市场基金  债券  股份
Money market funds, bonds, stocks,
大盘股  小盘股  国库券
large cap, small cap, treasuries.
由你来决定你愿意承担的风险预测
You decide the risk profile you're willing to take,
再把你选好的文件公证
get your elective deferral documents notarized,
一切就搞定了
and you'll be all set.
小菜一碟
Easy peasy.
你就是那个助手对吧
Hey, you're the helper guy, right?
是的  我是助教
The T.A., yeah.
我对这篇论文上的分数有点疑问
Yeah, I don't understand my grade on this paper.
这是个"D"
That would be a "D".
谢了  我知道  但是为什么只得了这个分数
Yeah, no, thanks, I get that. Um, but why?
是我拼错了"坦尼森"还是别的什么
I mean, I misspelled Tennyson or something?
对了  我记得你这篇论文
Uh, yeah, I remember this one.
分是我打的
I graded it.
是你  打的分  不是教授
Oh, you... you graded it, not the professor?
终身教授不改大一新生的调研论文
Tenured professors don't grade freshman class survey papers.
好吧  就算你是改的
Okay, so if you graded it,
那我这论文有什么问题吗
what was wrong with it?
写得很烂
Uh, it sucked.
很烂
It's sucked?
我  我论及了作业要求的所有内容
Um, look, I... I covered everything the assignment asked for.
这篇论文投机取巧
It was facile and glib.
虽然你泛泛而谈又故作高深
You danced around and you tried to be clever,
但通篇没有什么亮点见解
but there were no compelling insights
或是独到观点
or any attempt at original thought.
关于拜伦
Oh, original thought on Byron's
《恰尔德·哈洛尔德游记》的独到见解
Childe Harold's Pilgrimage?
听着  从维多利亚女王时代起
Look, nobody's had an original thought on Childe Harold
还没人能对恰尔德·哈洛尔德有什么独到见解
since Queen Victoria was still getting laid.
听着  这篇就是狗屎  明白了吗  你东拼西凑
Look, this was crap, okay? You threw it together.
以为别人注意不到  但是我留意到了
You thought nobody would notice, but I noticed.
你为什么要选修这门课
Why are you taking this class anyway?
因为这是唯一一门
Because it was the only
大一新生在午后能上的课
freshman English class available after noon.
听着  在你栽在这门课之前
Well, look, you got another week to add/drop
你还有一周的时间去选择其他的课
before you're stuck in here, all right?
要是你不想写出比这篇狗屁文章更好的东西
You don't want to work any harder than this piece of shit,
我劝你还是另选其他课的好
I suggest you find yourself another course.
斯坦
Yo, Stan.
我听说你身体不适
I hear you're not feeling so good.
斯坦
Stan.
这是搞什么飞机  伙计  他都死了
Hey, what the fuck, man? He's dead!
-哪一个  -斯坦  斯坦·柯普切克
- Which one? - Stan! Stan Kopchek!
是他啊  节哀顺变
Yeah. Sorry for your loss.
-他是你家人吗  -不  算是吧
- You family? - No... yeah... sort of.
是这样的  我们不能在电话里
Yeah, well, we're not supposed to tell people over the phone
告诉亲属病人已逝  所以我们通常只说
when a patient dies, so we usually just say
他们身体不适
they ain't feeling good.
他妈的他尸体都僵硬了
He's fucking cold!
杰奎因  他没来上通宵晚班
Joaquin, he ain't never show up for his overnight shift,
所以我们不知道他躺在那里  死了多久
so we don't know how long he's been laying up in there, dead.
我们这里有太平间  需要我帮你叫他们派人过来吗
We got a mortuary you need me to call for you?
运送尸体
Pick up the body?
弗兰克怎么样  你听到他有什么响动吗
How's Frank? You hear anything out of him?
没有  压根儿没看到他人影
No, no. No, not a peep.
我弄来了你想要的东西  烹饪喷雾剂  漏斗
I got the stuff you wanted, cooking spray, funnel.
我一喝酒
I have these things in my throat that bleed
我喉咙里的东西就会流血
if I try to swallow alcohol,
所以我得想别的法子把酒输入我的身体
so I have to figure out other ways to get it into my system.
-你就不能戒了吗  -不行
- You can't just stop? - No.
我全身打冷颤  情况很严重  我可能会死
I get the shakes, very bad. I could die.
我只能慢慢戒酒
I have to stop drinking slowly, over time.
所以我们要把这个装置连接起来
So we just hook up this handy-dandy contraption.
酒倒入这个袋子
Alcohol goes in this bag,
通过这个输入肛门
this goes up the poop chute, and voila.
加拉格家的人要喝酒不止一种法子
More than one way to get booze into a Gallagher.
帮  帮我个忙  好吗  儿子
Do... do me a favor, will you, son?
去楼下厨房  看看菲奥娜买了些什么
Go down to the kitchen and see what Fiona's got down there.
啤酒  红酒什么的  越烈的酒效果越好
Beer, wine. The hard stuff works best,
任何远程易燃物都派得上用场
but anything even remotely flammable will work.
你好
Hello.
你  还好吧
Ho... how you doing?
还行  你呢
Good. You?
也不错
Good.
你怀孕了  怎么可能
You're pregnant? How is that even possible?
我也是这么说的
Well, that's what I said.
我们养不起两个孩子
We can't afford to have two babies.
养一个都很勉强
We're barely gonna be able to afford to have one.
你告诉小凯了吗  你妈那边怎么办
Have you told Kev yet? What about your mom?
她得去堕胎了
Oh, she gonna have to have an abortion.
等我抱着自己的小小凯时
I can't have her nasty, Kev-mama baby staring up at me,
可不希望他们那个恶心的爱的结晶盯着我
not with my own Kev baby on my hip.
最后我肯定得恨死那个孩子
I'll just end up hating the mama baby
搞不好就把他碾死在街上了
and accidentally on purpose run over it in the driveway.
是迈克
It's Mike.
他要我今晚去他家
He wants me to come over to his place tonight,
庆祝我在公司工作满三个月
celebrate my three months at the company.
怎么个庆祝法  一屁股坐他脸上
Oh, celebrate how, by having you sit on his face?
之类的吧
Yeah, something like that.
你真的还没跟他睡过吗
You really haven't slept with him?
没  但应该快了
No, but I probably should soon.
他对一起出去吃饭已经没有兴趣了
He's already well past the whole 2 grand in meals thing
次次都要我来"灭火"
for me having to put out.
你让这事听着好像做家务
You make it sound like a chore.
我知道  很疯狂
I know, it's crazy,
但他是我的老板
but he's my boss, you know?
如果我们分手了怎么办
I mean, what happens if we break up?
你都已经帮他打过飞机了
You already gave him a hand job.
现在才担心这个太迟了吧
I think you long past the "what if we break up" point.
是吧  你应该是对的
Yeah, you're probably right.
你走吧  我帮你看孩子
You should go. I'll keep an eye on the kids.
-我需要练习带小孩  -可不  双倍的练习
- I need the kid practice now. - Yeah, times two.
好了  我... 我明天会回来的
All right, well, I'll be... I'll be back tomorrow.
我可以把厨房部分都清理干净
I can tackle this whole kitchen area.
得花几天时间  但我会把它拿下的
It may take a few days, but I will make this kitchen my bitch.
晚安啦
Now, good night.
你雇了希拉当女佣吗
You hired Sheila to be your maid?
没有  她只是经常来串门罢了
No, she's just been hanging around.
我觉得她是寂寞了
I think she's lonely.
你打算什么时候告诉小凯
So when are you gonna tell Kev?
我觉得还是等等吧
Mm, I figured I'd give it a bit,
看看再过几个月
see if this thing's still
它还能不能保住
hanging around after a couple of months.
我一直都不是适宜
I haven't exactly been fertile ground
种植小小凯的肥沃土地
for planting little, baby Kev seedlings.
你得告诉他  小维
You got to tell him, V.
瞒着他不公平
It's not fair to keep it a secret.
-妈的  -你在找什么
- Shit. - What are you looking for?
我们剩下的酒去哪了
I thought we had some wine left.
那天晚上我俩喝光了
Did the two of us finish off
整整一加仑的酒吗
an entire gallon of box wine the other night?
把它举得高且稳
Hold it up nice and high.
好了  把阀门打开
Okay, open the valve.
宝贝  你好了吗
Hey, babe, are you straight?
好了
Yeah, I'm good.
过来
Come here.
老天
Oh, Christ.
把门关上
Close the damn door!
没人想看见那个"黑鸟"
Nobody wants to see that mandingo shit.
我操
Fuck!
操
Oh, fuck!
Ah, fuck!
操
Fuck.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
滑倒了
I slipped.
快点  我要用厕所
Hurry up. I need to use the toilet.
保佑我们  主啊  您的这些礼物
Bless us, o lord, and these thy gifts,
我们将通过基督赐予的恩惠接收
which we are about to receive through the bounty of Christ,
我们的主啊  阿门
our lord, amen.
愿主为他人的需求显灵
May the lord provide for the wants of others.
老天呀
Oh, God.
老天
太爽了  谢谢你
That was great. Thank you.
你刚才棒极了
You were great.
你一直都很棒
You are great.
你...
Hey, do you, uh...
你需要我... 帮你做点什么吗
do you need me to do anything... something else for you?
什么
What?
就是抚摸你什么的
Well, you know, like, touch you or whatever.
不不  不用  我很好
No. No, I'm... I'm good.
那真是好极了
That's really good.
你上哪去
Where are you going?
我要去拿之前
I'm gonna go get that
答应给你的香槟
bottle of champagne that I promised you.
-我得回家了  -不
- I've got to go home. - No.
孩子们还要上学呢
It's a school night.
不不  拜托啦  就喝一杯
No, no, no. Come on, one glass.
你死不了的
That's not gonna kill you.
而且酒庄的员工说这酒很不错
Plus, you know, the guy at the store said it was pretty good.
只是很不错而已吗
Just pretty good?
好到一瓶
Yeah, well, really good is, like,
得花掉我租车一个月的钱
a month of my car lease or something.
一杯  就喝一杯
One glass. One glass.
-就一杯  -好极了
- One glass. - Yes.
谢谢你请我吃晚餐  我很开心
Well, thanks for dinner. I had a great time.
我很爱吃熊猫速食
I love Panda Express.
我也是  我也爱吃
Yeah, me, too. I do, too.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我也喜欢你
I... I like you, too.
那是你爸吗
Oh, is... is that your dad?
不  他是我姐的朋友
Uh, no, a friend of my sister's.
他人很好
He's nice.
是吧  他...看起来挺好的
Yeah, he... he looks nice.
我不确定  但我好像看见
I'm not sure, but I think
黛比跟一个小子坐在外面的车里
Debbie's sitting out front in a car with some dude.
这个男的减了大概两百磅
This dude lost, like, 200 pounds,
看起来还是像头搁浅的鲸鱼
and he still looks like a beached whale.
老天  看看他多余的皮肤
Oh, jeez. Look at all that extra skin.
割下都能做个行李箱了
You could cut it off and make a suitcase.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing over here?
菲奥娜跟麦克出去了  我帮她带孩子
Watching the kids while Fiona's out with Mike.
斯坦死了
Stan died.
什么
What?
疗养院给我来了电话
They called me from the nursing home.
明天一早我就得去停尸房
I got to go to the mortuary tomorrow morning
还要给他选副棺材什么的
and pick out a casket and all that stuff.
宝贝  我很抱歉
Oh, baby, I'm so sorry.
晚安啦
So, good night.
好  好  晚安
Yeah. Yeah, have a good night.
回来啦  小黛
Hey, Debs.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
什么
What?
我以为我听到你说你怀孕了
I thought you just said you're pregnant.
我说了
I did.
搞什么鬼  你认真的吗
Holy shit, are you serious?
是的  但我们不该抱太大希望
Yes, but we shouldn't get our hopes up.
搞什么鬼
Holy shit!
我们会有两个小孩
We're gonna have two?
-你是在整我吗  -不是
- Are you fucking with me? - No.
那是真的咯
Are you serious?
-宝贝  -我知道...
- Baby! - I kno...
有小宝贝啦
Baby!
卡尔
Carl.
儿子
Son.
你最好轻一点
Probably want to go a little easier.
像捧个蛋一样轻
Hold it like an egg.
还是不行
It's not working.
也许你该让它休息一下
Maybe you need to give it a rest.
这是今天第几次了
How many times is that today?
-第九次  -第九次
- Nine. - Nine.
你会把那可怜的小兄弟撸破皮的
You're gonna wear the poor thing out.
你用什么做润滑剂
What are you using for lubrication?
什么润滑剂
Lubrication?
不用润滑剂会起水泡的
You don't use lubricant, you get blisters.
相信我  我都经历过
Believe me, I know.
卡尔  可以在我不在房间里的时候撸吗
Carl, how about when I'm not in the room?
你一直在房间里
You're always in the room.
那就去浴室撸吧
Bathroom then.
来吧  宝贝  就尝尝味道
Come on, baby, just a taste.
只想尝尝味道
I just want a little taste.
干杯
L'Chaim.
你上哪去了  晚餐快好了
Hey, where you been? Dinner's almost ready.
好市多
Costco.
好市多  美国最大的连锁会员制仓储量贩店
为什么去好市多
Costco? Why?
买点东西
I needed something.
凡士林润肤露
员工请洗手